And yes, you're right.
I'm pissed whenever I see you.
Do you know why?
Because I remember what you did to me.
And every time I remember what you did to me,
I want to kick you and crush you
to fine pieces.
But it doesn't mean
that I don't want to see you anymore.
And that doesn't mean
that all my feelings for you
will just go away.
Even if you turn the world upside down,
it's still you who my heart wants.
- Don't you want it?
- Of course, I want to.
I can't hear it.
I like Florence.
Hey, neighbors, Florence has a boyfriend!
I like you.
I like Florence!
I'm going to a brunch,
so it's okay for me to skip breakfast.
Brunch? We know you'll be with Florence.
Just give her my kisses.
Me too, give her my hugs and kisses.
Me too, Nero.
Of course, don't forget Mr. Dencio...
But wait, Nero,
why did you pick me up this early?
What's happening?
Today is the first day to road happiness.
And I'm planning to celebrate that
with the longest date in history.
I'm so sorry to intrude,
but can I talk to Florence
for a couple of minutes?
In fairness, you have a fighting spirit.
But it's still wrong
that you resorted to blackmail.
Thank you, Florence.
You know what, the way that I see it,
it's Nero who won the jackpot
in your relationship.
You're awesome, Florence.
And truly,
I sincerely wish you and Nero happiness.
Who is she?
Her name is Florence Dela Cruz.
Do you remember the computer guy
who did an approximation
of your baby's appearance
if she happens to grow up?
Of course, I didn't believe
that the Computer Graphics Specialist
can approximate the appearance of Celestina
if she grows up into a young woman,
by uploading her baby picture.
Look.
That is the rendered picture.
That's Celestina's baby picture.
I have a strong feeling
that this is your missing daughter, Celestina.
I believe that this girl is my granddaughter.
I know you thought it was crazy,
but I already saw her in Levante.
I thought my eyes played tricks on me,
but then I saw her again
in Garpidio's mansion.
Grandpa Garp?
So you're Florence Dela Cruz?
Since then, I have been curious and obsessed.
She never disappeared from my sight.
Grilled Chicken Buddies for life!
Seriously, my daughter is still alive?
My daughter with Alyanna is still alive.
Celestina is still alive?
Yes.
Dad, where is she?
Where is she? I'll go to her. Where is she?
Lorenzo, calm down.
- Just take it easy.
- How can I calm down?
After all this time,
my daughter is still alive.
Lorenzo, please.
Just take it easy.
Look, we need to be careful
in dealing with this
or else we lose the opportunity
to get her back.
So what's your plan?
Okay, everyone,
make sure
that our vegetables are cut correctly and nicely,
especially you...
Florence and her parents are our visitors.
It's a shame
if the food we prepare is not delicious.
Serafica, relax.
They will not judge us as a top chef.
They know our capacity.
Take it easy. Things are going fine.
Oh my, Grandpa Garp.
Federico is so judgmental.
You said it.
It's like he's from the Supreme Court.
He's so judgmental.
Really? Seriously?
Don't appeal anymore.
You can go to the Court of Appeals
to show off.
Nero, what's that?
It looks like you're staring too much
at what you're cooking.
Tight guarding.
This is a special Adobo, Grandpa Garp.
It's Adobo without soy sauce,
just vinegar and salt.
Is that possible?
Why?
If there's no soy sauce,
you have to stare at it
thoroughly so it can be cooked?
Do you have a laser beam in your eyes?
"Do you have a laser beam in your eyes"?
You're being a smart alec.
That's dry Adobo.
You need to keep an eye on the meat.
Look, it gets cooked in its own fats.
It needs perfect timing.
What is this mess about?
Oh, you're here.
Come on, boys. Give us a hand.
Let's help finish this.
We're going to make a nice feast
for the family of Florence.
Come on! Help out.
What can you contribute?
I'll be making a Paella Valenciana
that is Paella Venduras and Paella Negra.
As for me, I'll make sushi.
- That's delicious.
- I'll take care of the mango pie.
Wow, delicious.
Florence, is it okay if we're bringing
cooked food there?
Yes, of course, Mother. Grandpa Garp is kind.
He'll appreciate this so much.
You know, I don't want to be judgmental,
but according to my judgment,
it seems there's no delicious food
cooked there.
That's why, they are relying on their chefs.
Florence, why are you dressed that way?
Later, you might look grumpy there.
Mother, it looks like we're going there
for an engagement.
And besides, the people there know me,
so even if I'm wearing a sack,
they will not judge me.
What? What do you mean by wearing a sack?
What's important is
you'll look presentable there.
I look presentable.
- No, you better prepare.
- I already look presentable!
And you too, Federico!
How come you're not yet dressed?
But how about my huge body?
Go ahead and change.
Hey, who is that?
Who is that?
The car is beautiful.
Grandpa Roger!
Almost 17 years ago...
A huge crime happened against my family.
Alyanna!
And no one here can imagine the pain.
And what's painful is
that they did not only take away
one life that day.
My grandchild?
My grandchild.
Where is the baby?
Have you seen a baby?
We didn't notice a baby.
Sir, did you notice anything there?
Nothing, Don Rogelio.
Lorenzo...
They found Alyanna.
She's gone.
How about Celestina?
They can't find her.
They never found her.
No one saw the baby.
So, everyone assumed
that my granddaughter died.
That Celestina was a victim too.
But there's always a part of me
that believed my grandchild is still alive.
Everybody thought I was crazy,
even my own son thought
that I was being unreasonable.
But no matter what everyone said,
that's what I believe
because that's what my heart is telling me.
And I was right.
And I was right because the moment I saw you,
my belief
that my granddaughter is still alive grew stronger.
And that's you, Florence.
You are my missing granddaughter.
You are Celestina Almero.
This is a huge mistake, Don Rogelio.
Florence is our daughter.
We are her real parents.
She's is really our daughter.
Our sympathies to the death of Alyanna
and your grandchild.
But this is a huge mistake.
Are you serious, Federico?
Can you stand by your lie?
Grandpa Roger, please.
Why are you doing this to us now?
Because that's the truth.
I came here to give your parents
a chance to come clean.
Don Rogelio.
We didn't do anything wrong.
Alright, then we have
to welcome an investigation.
The truth is I asked my son, Lorenzo,
to become reasonable
and don't do any drastic action.
That's why, he's not here.
And maybe that's for the better.
Because if Lorenzo was here,
he would be unreasonable.
That's why I'm here to give you a warning.
We're going to exhaust every legal remedy
to bring Florence back to her real family.
So you can be returned to us, the Almeros.
So, this is not the last time
you're going to see me.
Please don't do anything
that will put you in danger.
Did they arrive already?
I just called the guardhouse.
No one has arrived yet.
Excuse me, Grandpa Garp,
I'll just call Florence.
What are you doing?
We're leaving.
We'll go to a faraway place.
Federico, have you gone mad?
Didn't you hear what Don Rogelio said?
Let's not do anything
that will put us in danger.
Do you think we can escape from the Almeros?
I don't care.
They can't take my daughter from me.
Federico, think!
It's as if we're saying we committed a crime.
Mother, Father, can you please
explain to me what's happening?
Why is Grandpa Roger saying
that I'm his granddaughter?
Why is he saying that I'm an Almero?
Father, what's the truth?
The truth is...
your mother and I couldn't conceive a child.
No matter what we did,
we were never blessed with a baby
to complete our family.
I love your mother so much, but sometimes,
I can't avoid thinking about
my biggest failure to her
because I can't give her a child.
I'm sorry, Federico and Lydia.
But with your situation right now,
you can't have a child.
Is that you?
Huh? That's not me.
What was that?
Oh no...
Did you hear something?
What?
- Something is moving in the back.
- Huh?
What's that?
Hold on...
Oh no, what's that?
We just thought...
that you are the answer to our prayers.
That you're heaven-sent.
That you are the baby
we've been asking from God.
We closed our eyes...
and didn't bother to ask how a baby ended up
in the back of the delivery truck
I was driving.
And we promised
that we will love you completely.
That we will love you like our own daughter.
- Sorry...
- Florence?
Florence!
Nero?
Florence?
Nero.
Why does it seem
like you always show up at the perfect time?
Whenever I need you, you suddenly appear.
I was calling you earlier.
I wanted to ask why you haven't arrived.
But when you didn't answer,
I decided to go to you.
Did Grandpa Garp get mad
that we failed to make it?
Don't think about that.
I'll explain it to them.
I'm sorry
your plans didn't push through again.
I'm also sorry if I can't stop crying.
There's no reason for you to be sorry.
Just cry.
I'm always here by your side.
Nero, what should I do?
The truth is I don't know what to do.
I don't know what I should feel.
How would I feel
if everything I believed while growing up
suddenly collapsed,
and everything is not true?
Should I get mad at Mother and Father
because they lied to me?
Florence...
Or should I turn my back on them
and go to my real family?
Or should I tell the Almeros
to stop bothering us
and just let me be,
because I'm not their missing granddaughter?
I'm not an Almero.
I'm a Dela Cruz and that's the real me.
That's the truth I believed, Nero.
But...
why is this happening to me?
I've been doing okay.
I'm happy with my life
with my father and mother.
I don't need this kind of complication.
Did I do something wrong?
Did I do something bad
for all this to happen to me?
Florence, it's not your fault.
Bad things happen even to good people.
If only...
If only I can give you my heart,
so I'd be the one to feel
all the heaviness and pain
you're feeling right now.
Let it be me.
Just let it be me.
What happened? What was their reaction?
Denial.
Looking desperate at their attempt
to stand by their lies.
Why didn't you bring Celestina home?
Firstly, her name is Florence.
I don't think she'll respond
to the name Celestina.
So whether we like it or not,
we need to recognize the fact
that she grew up
with a different identity,
with a different family.
Secondly, she must come to us on her own.
She should voluntarily come to us.
Because if we force her,
the more she'll resist being an Almero.
How can we be assured
that she'll come to us voluntarily?
Look, for all I know, maybe her fake parents
are packing their things
so they can take my daughter away.
Baste is there.
And I have people who are spying
and looking after the Dela Cruz family.
That's why, even if they leave,
I can follow them wherever they go.
But how can we be so sure
that Celestina will come here,
I mean, Florence?
Florence is a very smart girl.
She knows what is at stake here.
I think she can figure it out on her own.
The moment she realizes the consequences
of the things the parents she recognizes
are doing right now,
she will make the right decision
for everybody.
What if she won't do it?
What if she won't come here?
She has nowhere to hide.
I will personally look for her
and drag her back here.
Florence?
My child.
Have you eaten?
I'll prepare food for you.
No need, Mother.
I'm okay.
Where is Nero? Why didn't you let him in?
I told him to go home
and apologize to Grandpa Garp on our behalf
for failing to go for dinner.
By the way, Florence.
We spoke to Iking earlier.
He knows a lawyer
who can help us with our situation.
We'll talk to the lawyer right away
so we'd find out what's the best thing to do
with our situation right now.
Can we really do it, Mother?
Can we afford to pay a lawyer?
You heard what Don Rogelio said, right?
They won't stop until they get you back.
We won't easily give in, Florence.
We're not related, but you're still my child.
We're one family here.
You're connected to our hearts.
I won't allow them
to take you away from us just like that.
Mother, just let it be.
I'll talk to them first.
I'll talk to Grandpa Roger.
And if they really see me as an Almero,
their granddaughter,
maybe they will listen to me, right?
But, Florence...
Don't worry, Mother.
I can do this.
I'm cause of this problem,
that's why I can find a way to solve this.
Don't cry, Mother.
We love you so much.
I noticed the first time I saw Florence
that she looks kind of familiar.
She had this uncanny resemblance
to the late Alyanna Almero.
So, you're Florence Dela Cruz.
Sorry if I was surprised
because when I saw you,
I remembered someone.
Still, it's unbelievable
that the missing daughter of Lorenzo
is Florence Dela Cruz.
How is Florence?
You know, Florence, Grandpa.
She'll overcome everything
that is thrown at her.
Yes, but this situation is very difficult.
Her parents, Lydia and Federico,
they're in a lot of trouble.
Most likely they'll be accused
that they had something to do
with the death of Alyanna Almero.
That's what I'm afraid of, Grandpa.
Tell Florence
that we're ready to help with whatever she needs.
We won't think twice about it,
and will help her.
She's family and we always protect our own.
Thank you, Grandpa.
I'll let her know that.
According to our lawyer,
there will be a preliminary investigation.
Was there a crime committed?
What were the facts of the case?
And how did Celestina end up...
with the Dela Cruz Family.
Sir, you have a visitor.
Hello.
Good day.
I'm sorry... I'm sorry.
You remind me so much of your mother.
You know what?
She should be proud of you, Celestina...
I'm sorry, I mean Florence.
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry if I'm being emotional...
because I never thought I'd see you again.
I told you, the moment you see Florence,
there'll be no denying that she is an Almero.
Have a seat.
Have you met your grandfather?
Have a seat. Have you eaten?
Do you want something to drink?
Baste?
- Yes, Sir?
- Get us something to drink.
Yes, Sir.
Actually, the reason why I'm here now...
is that I want to talk to both of you.
I want to talk to you
about my mother and father.
So...
did we do well last night?
It was okay,
it managed to get in the top five.
- Top five?
- Yup.
Didn't I even reach the semis?
Perhaps next time, you'll be the champion.
Then I'll work even harder.
Stop it!
What? What are you looking at?
- Nothing.
- Huh?
You're envious again?
Better yet, find your own love.
Or maybe you better hurry with that,
because our wards are hungry.
Dencio, Ms. Serafica, James and Patotina.
- Do you know about the latest?
- What?
The latest trending topic?
What, what?
Latest trending topic? I know that.
The Lakers are the champion.
Wrong.
And don't count LBJ,
they won't win the championship.
This is hotter.
The oil prices have gone down.
Yes, that's it.
Wrong.
Madam, don't hope
that the oil prices will go down.
You're like a virgin
who believes in the love of the...
I know it!
The wages of the workers have increased.
- That's it.
- Right!
Wrong!
Someone transferred to Kapuso Network?
- That's it.
- That's right. That's possible.
Wrong.
This one, I'm sure about this one.
There's a sixth member of the Voltes 5.
That's it.
Wrong! What, 6? Voltes 6?
This one.
Finally, the crow has turned white,
and the stork has turned black, right?
- Yes, that's right.
Just a little more push
and you'll finally get it.
Why don't you say it?
You're full of nonsense.
You keep on cutting corners.
There's a news bulletin,
a hot item, what's that about?
That's what you get.
You're so impatient, Madam.
What? What?
Okay, I'm going to say it. Here it goes.
Okay?
- Go ahead.
- Okay?
Okay.
Did you know...
that Florence Dela Cruz...
is the missing grandchild of the Almeros?
What?
Are you sure Florence is an Almero?
Dude, that's not a good joke.
Are you saying she's the child
of the enemy of our family?
I'm sure Nero will not joke about that.
How did that happen?
Based on Florence's story,
her mother, Lydia, and father, Federico,
accidentally found her.
So our assumption is
on the night Alyanna Almero was killed,
she was able to hide her daughter,
and it was Ms. Lydia and Mr. Federico
who found her.
You know what this means, right?
Things are about to get complicated
between Nero and Florence.
Especially with you, because you're a Ferell.
I'm sorry, Florence...
But we have a reason to believe
that your parents have something to do
with the death of your real mother,
who is Alyanna.
Our theory is
they're part of the group
who victimized you and your mother that day.
But somehow, they could not do it.
Something happened
and they decided to keep you alive.
What you're thinking is wrong.
My father and mother
can't possibly have done that.
My parents are not capable of doing that.
I grew up with them.
So if there's someone who knows them,
that's me.
And I can tell you
that they didn't do anything wrong.
The little thing that we have,
they give everything to me.
They endure sleeping on a small bed
while I sleep on a bigger one.
The food they're about to eat,
they give it all to me.
They opted to prioritize my studies
than think about themselves.
Their only fault here
is they adopted the baby
whom they thought was abandoned.
Let's just say
that what you're saying is true,
that they have nothing to do
with what happened to Alyanna.
But they committed a lot of violations.
They kept you
even if they knew you weren't their daughter,
when the correct thing to do should've been
to report you to the authorities.
And most likely they faked some documents
to make it
look like you're their real daughter.
Let's assume
that they have nothing to do with the crime.
They were at the wrong place
at the wrong time...
but they have a huge criminal liability.
They have to answer that to the law.
That's why I'm here right now.
I'm begging you.
Is it their fault
that they wanted to become parents
because they suddenly have a chance
to be a mother and father?
Is it their fault
that they gave so much love to a child
whom they thought was abandoned?
Is it their fault
that they created a family whom they thought
is the answer to their prayers
because they can't have children?
Oh, Florence.
- Oh, Florence. Please stand up.
- I'm begging you.
I know there's something you can do
to help my mother and father
in this situation.
I just want to repay the love they gave me
ever since I was a baby
when I got separated from you.
I will do everything to help
and protect my mother and father.
That's why I'm begging you,
help me protect them.
Are you okay?
I was feeling so bad imagining
the kind of life you grew up with.
But when you showed that kind of love
for your mother and father...
I was reassured.
For you to do that...
it seems they raised you with so much love.
I just finished talking to the lawyer.
I'm going to make some calls
and sweep all this under the rug.
This means they will no longer
investigate your parents.
Thank you.
Florence, I know how much
you love your mother and father...
but that doesn't change the fact
that you're a real Almero.
Look, I could never bring myself
to get married again
after your mommy died.
That means...
you're the only heir
to whatever your grandfather and I have.
What do you want me to do?
In exchange for withdrawing the case
against your mother and father...
you will live in this house...
and you will forget being a Dela Cruz.
Because from now on, you're a real Almero.
Mr. Baste, are those my things?
What will you do?
I'm replacing all your old clothes
with new ones.
Outfits that suit you better.
And as for this...
let's change this to a newer model
with more secure connection.
Baste, you take care of that.
Grandsons, you must understand
that the Almeros are a very proud family.
They're one of the oldest families,
and they are very sensitive
with their reputation.
And now that Florence is with them,
I'm sure she's going to be changed
and become an Almero.
- Florence, can we talk?
- Can we talk later?
I'll just find a way to talk to you.
We're your friends, Florence.
We're not a threat.
- Are you okay? Are they treating you well?
- Hey, don't push.
- Don't push us.
- Hey, that's enough.
Mister, they're not my enemies.
Don't do that.
Don't!